I can no longer care for it. Please take it.}
[top banner]Hanamaro Drills/[white bubble below]Math/[white letter blue ray-left]All done!/[white letter in blue ray-right]Fun!}
Yomogi Preschool}
Kudo}
European Pastries [flower] Chiroru}
Gabu Jougasaki}
,“subete migaite aru miteru“ ---->“subete idaite aruiteru“/??????????/I embrace them all and continue to walk}}
Fujimoto Kiyokazu}
Summertime Memories}
Oh!
What a cute little kitten, Ioryogi-san!
Hmph!
“I can no longer care for it. Please take it.”
Don’t you dare get another one of your ideas!
It’s so soft and cuddly!
And you just went ahead and did it!
But I can’t leave this little kitten all by itself!
Then what are you going to do about it?
I’ll do this!
This way, the kitten won’t be all alone, and I’ll be able to find people to heal!
So you’ll spend the rest of your miserable life here?!
Acting like you have no problems of your own to deal with.
And now you’re caring for a kitten? What a joke!
But I can’t just leave it by itself.
Now we have a stray cat?
You’re wrong! The owner said it can no longer be cared for!
It’s the same thing.
If you aren’t willing to care for it to the end, then leave it alone.
He’s mean.
But he’s right.
Kittie?
Wh-What’s wrong?!
It’s obviously hungry.
Chiho-chan… what’s the answer to number five?
Huh? You don’t know either, Chise?
Coming!
Ah!
Kobato-san!
Good day to you!
I need food, now!
Mama is out right now.
This is all we have.
Um, too much sugar will be…
Huh?
Oh, I wasn’t referring to me! It’s…
It’s for this kitten.
Oh!
How cute!
It seems the owner can’t take care of it anymore.
If you have any food you can share with it…
Shhh!
Can we go to your room?
Yes.
It really seems to like it!
Thank goodness!
Um, why are you two talking in such hushed voices?
This apartment building forbids pets.
Someone who lived here once had a dog,
who barked so loud that
the neighbors complained.
After that…
…Mama began refusing to let the tenants keep any pets.
So I can’t take care of it here.
Why don’t you ask the owner to take it back?
I don’t know the owner.
I found the kitten in a box
with no name written on it.
Really? Then, if this keeps up,
the kitten will be all alone again.
It would be a good idea to find a new owner…
Tomorrow, I’ll ask Sayaka-sensei at Yomogi Preschool!
Sayaka-san is sure to agree!
And we’ll get to see the kitten there anytime!
So now we have to give it a name!
Kobato-san? What would be good?
Huh? Me?!
Uh… um…
I can’t think of anything that quickly!
Since it’s milky white, how about Milk?
And it loves milk too!
Milk? That’s an adorable name! It’s wonderful!
Hmph!
How cute!
It sure is!
And its name is Milk!
Huh…
Come here, Milk!
I want to hold it too!
Me too!
Let me pet it!
Looks like everyone’s enjoying it.
So we can keep it here?
Yuzuru-kun!
Come with me for a second.
Are you all right?
Yuzuru is allergic to cats, isn’t he?
Allergic… to cats?
It means he sneezes, gets a rash and if it’s really bad, gets asthmatic.
Sayaka-sensei…
We can’t have a cat in this preschool.
You’re right.
Kobato-chan, I’m really sorry.
See how much trouble you caused everyone by being so impulsive?
Impulsive?
So will you take care of it yourself?
Fujimoto-kun!
You’ll never feel complete if you only do things for your own satisfaction.
You’re just as bad as the
person who abandoned it.
I’m sorry, Kobato-chan.
I’m fine now.
I’m really sorry too.
You idiot!
Don’t play with me! I may look
like a stuffed animal, but I’m not!
Kobato-chan? So you were here?
Sayaka-sensei!
Can I sit next to you?
Yes.
I’m sorry to disappoint you.
Don’t be. I’m the one who should be sorry.
Fujimoto-kun means well.
He probably…
…sees a part of himself in that kitten.
Huh?
Oh, nevermind. I’ll help look for a new owner for that kitten.
Don’t you fret. I’m sure we’ll find someone.
Yes.
So, what are you going to do now?
I’ll look for Milk’s new owner!
I will not cause trouble for everyone!
Count me in.
Especially since I’m getting it bad here.
Bye-bye!
Sayaka-san!
Hello!
Is Milk around?
An allergy to cats?
Yes. I’m sorry.
It’s all right.
I think we should ask Mama.
We can’t. Pets are forbidden.
Asking her would only bother her.
You’re right.
Is there anyone who will take care of this little kitten?
Please be this kitten’s new owner!
Please take care of this kitt…
Kobato-san!
Chiho-chan! Chise-chan!
Come here, Milk!
Have you been good?
I’m sorry, I tried asking Sayaka-sensei…
We just came from the preschool.
Huh?
It’s not your fault, Kobato-chan.
But I haven’t found anyone who will take it home.
The two of us will search with you!
Milk, we promise we’ll find you a new owner.
I’m sorry.
I already have my hands full with the kids.
Oh, Katherine, what’s wrong?
Kobato-san!
Let’s go!
E-Excuse us!
Can’t you salesmen ever leave me alone?!
Oh… huh?
Milk!
Doumoto-san!
Kobato-chan?
Milk!
Come here!
Wow, that’s amazing!
So you want someone to take in that kitten?
Yes.
Everyone here lives alone.
I’m out of ideas, but I’ll
help you look for someone.
Thank you very much. I seem to
cause trouble for everyone I meet.
It’s no trouble for us.
You’re putting a lot of effort into this,
and people want to help out.
But that’s not...
But you really shouldn’t go
knocking on strangers’ doors.
But Fujimoto-san told me that I wouldn’t feel complete,
if I only did things for my own satisfaction.
That I’m like the person who abandoned it.
Will that guy ever change?
Forget what he said.
I don’t think anyone really wants to abandon such a cute little kitten.
There must be some other reason for it.
But Fujimoto-san seemed really gloomy when he said that.
So Fujimoto-san is right in saying I can’t be half-hearted about this.
I should do what I can with all I have.
Oh, this time we’ll go to the homes of the people we know and ask them.
Okay, if anything happens,
give me a call on my cell.
Yes! Thank you very much!
They don’t seem to be home.
He’s taking a break.
Since we handle food here, having a cat…
Is that so?
Sorry I can’t help.
Hello, Mihara residence.
Sayaka?
Huh? A kitten?
I really wish we could keep it here…
So those girls have been…
Yes, understood. Bye.
Oh?
It has really gotten dark.
And Milk is all tuckered out.
Milk?
Ah! It’s hungry again!
Ready… go!
This one!
It’s pathetic how I can’t do anything.
So we can’t even buy some stupid cat food?
No!
Say, Chise-chan?
What?
We really should ask Mama.
Yes, I’m sure she will let you keep it.
Then tonight we can sleep together with Milk!
Yes, with Kobato-san too!
Yes!
Oh?
She was there when…
Oh my.
The girl with that wonderful song.
Do you know her, Kobato-san?
Yes!
Um… how’s the baby?
Since she’s off from work today, his mother is looking after him.
Is that so?
Still, why did you come here?
I heard that a girl, who was searching for someone to take in a kitten, lives here.
Eh?
Oh my!
What a lovely kitten!
It’s so small and so cute!
Is there any way I can take
this little one home with me?
Do you really mean it?
Of course. My grandchild is an only child,
so if he had a kitten to play with…
But…
…there are people who sneeze and get rashes when they touch cats.
Will the baby be all right?
That pizza man was worried about the same thing.
Pizza man?
Yes.
After making each delivery, he would
earnestly ask if they could take in a kitten.
I heard him asking while I was passing by.
Fujimoto-san did that...
My grandson just loves animals.
So there are no cat allergies.
Oh my!
Isn’t that great, Milk?
You won’t be alone any more!
Well then…
Bye-bye, Milk!
We’ll come visit!
Wait, Lady!
Here’s Milk’s food!
My, it was well looked after.
Please take care of Milk.
Please.
The room seems much bigger without Milk here with us.
Yeah!
And what a relief!
What th-?
Milk’s milkbowl.
I’m sure Chiho-chan and Chise-chan feel like I do.
Where’re you going?
Oh!
Kobato-san?
Good evening!
Um…
Chiho and Chise are up on the roof.
I wonder if Milk is being loved.
She seemed like such a nice old lady.
Everything will be fine with her.
Kobato-san?
That’s…
I forgot to give it back.
Milk’s… milkbowl…
Yes!
Come to think of it, when I first met that lady, there was a full moon too.
The cherry blossoms were
blooming ever so beautifully.
The baby she was taking for a walk,
wouldn’t stop crying.
I tried consoling the baby…
Wah!
But I only made him cry even more!
And then what happened?
Then… I sang a song.
Eh?
You sing, Kobato-san?
Yes!
Then after that, the baby stopped crying.
What did you sing?
Eh?
Let’s see…
I want to hear it!
I want to hear it too!
Huh?
Let us hear it, Kobato-san!
Please!
Yes!
That song…
What now?
I want to thank you for trying to help Milk!
It got a wonderful new owner!
And it’s all thanks to you, Fujimoto-san.
That’s all you wanted?
Yes!
What are you doing?!
I just remembered something important!
Could you perhaps lend me a phone?
Then, could you call me back if
you know someone who likes cats?
Sure, thanks.
Kiyokazu?
Hello?
Um… well…
Uh… Kobato-chan? What happened?
Yes! W-Well, we found someone
who was willing to take in the kitten!
I just wanted to let you know.
Really?
Yes! Fujimoto-san found her for us!
Kiyokazu did?
I see.
I’m sorry to make you worry.
Don’t be. I’m glad.
Bye.
There’s more.
But why?
The one who found the new
owner for Milk was Fujimoto-san.
I didn’t do anything to help-
Of course you weren’t any stinkin’ help!
You just had to bring home that kitten and cause people pain!
Yes. It’s all my fault that I caused trouble for everyone and made them worry!
Well, you spend money to make money.
That’s how the world works.
Huh?
You sang that song to Chiho and Chise after seeing,
how sad they were without that kitten.
I was only telling them about that lady and the baby-
And those feelings you
relayed soothed their spirits.
So I can heal people through songs as well?
But still…
My ear is still not healed!
Because of that!
A big fat zero, Kobato!
Oh, but since it’s a circle, it looks like the moon!
Quit being so damn happy!
Oh yeah, and Milk’s milkbowl is
also a circle! They all go together!
Fine then! You like circles so much, all
you’re gonna get are zeros from now on!
That’s mean, Ioryogi-san!